[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110307pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 35, "question": "I mean where is the damage to the show here from Charlie's behavior off screen?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "WRB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "POS", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 36, "answer": "Well, the damage to the show is they can't produce a show.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Charlie"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110307pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", ":", "RB", "RB", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 71, "question": "To replace them with somebody else?", "question_pos_tagged": ["TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 72, "answer": "Incredibly enough -- incredibly enough it does usually work.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110307pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 83, "question": "Is Charlie Sheen employable anymore in television in America?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "NNP", "NNP", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 84, "answer": "Well, I think he is.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Charlie Sheen"], "LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Charlie Sheen"]}, "docId": "110307pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "NN", "NN", ",", "NNP", ",", "IN", "POS", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 90, "question": "Do you think that Charlie is still bankable?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 91, "answer": "With all due respect to your wonderful career and reality television, Piers, that's really the only thing that's left for Charlie Sheen right now.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Charlie"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Janice", "Charlie"], "LOCATION": ["Janice"]}, "docId": "110307pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", ":", "VB", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", ",", "VB", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "NNP", "RB", "IN", "WRB", "NNP", "NN", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "IN", ",", "RB", ",", "IN", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 123, "question": "Charlie Sheen, who knows?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 124, "answer": "I mean, Janice -- let me bring in, let me bring in Janice here because when Charlie sat here with me a week ago, actually, in one of the breaks, I said you're on Twitter.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Charlie Sheen"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110307pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBN", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "RB", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 131, "question": "Isn't he?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 132, "answer": "Well, listen, I also think he's become a little bit of a folk hero to some people, you know, whether we like it or not.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110307pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", ":"], "qSentId": 162, "question": "Wouldn't yours be, Howard?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "RB", "VB", "VB", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 163, "answer": "I don't --", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Howard"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110307pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 171, "question": "Yes or no, Howard?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "CC", "DT", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 172, "answer": "In some form, probably yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Howard"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110307pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 175, "question": "Bill Carter?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 176, "answer": "Within a year, I'd say yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Carter"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110307pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 177, "question": "And Steve?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 178, "answer": "Maybe on a reality show a year from now.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Steve"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110307pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 193, "question": "Is he nice?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 194, "answer": "He's very nice.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110307pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 239, "question": "But what's your personal view of Charlie?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 240, "answer": "I have no comment on it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110307pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 241, "question": "No view of him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 242, "answer": "I do, but I have no comment on the show about it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110307pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", ":", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 244, "question": "No?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "aSentId": 245, "answer": "Well, I just think it would be -- it wouldn't be right for any of us to comment about it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110307pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "TO", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 253, "question": "You're called the talk ladies, aren't you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "NNS", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 254, "answer": "Not to us.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110307pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 255, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 256, "answer": "We haven't talked about it not once.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110307pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 257, "question": "None of you talked about Charlie Sheen?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 258, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Charlie Sheen"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110307pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 265, "question": "Sharon is famous for going who?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "VBG", "WP", "."], "aSentId": 266, "answer": "Well, I know you've talked about him.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110307pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "CC", ":"], "qSentId": 293, "question": "Does it really matter how somebody behaves in their private lives when it comes to the performance on a TV show?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "JJR", "WRB", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NNS", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 294, "answer": "You want to take that or --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110307pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "DT", "JJS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 313, "question": "That's the hard bit, isn't it, for a parent when you have a child that's gone off the rails whatever age they are?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 314, "answer": "Yes, I think, speaking as a parent, you only want the best for your child.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110307pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 325, "question": "He's not?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 326, "answer": "No, he's about 44.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110307pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 342, "question": "He has, what, five kids?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", ",", "WP", ",", "CD", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 343, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "110307pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "NN", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 355, "question": "I mean aren't our news values a bit warped?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBP", "RB", "PRP$", "NN", "NNS", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 356, "answer": "You should answer that because you do breaking news, Piers.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110307pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 369, "question": "So it's about the ratings?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 370, "answer": "Well, no, actually.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110307pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 374, "question": "You know, is it right to castigate Charlie Sheen now again for alleged misdemeanors against women, for example?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "TO", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "RB", "RB", "IN", "VBN", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", ",", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 375, "answer": "Well, you know, it's like I said.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Charlie Sheen"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110307pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 412, "question": "Have you not?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 413, "answer": "Never.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110307pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJS", "."], "qSentId": 443, "question": "Right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 444, "answer": "I think like two times a week at least.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110307pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 448, "question": "I'm like, oh, what is Sharon going to do today?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", ",", "JJ", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "NNP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 449, "answer": "It's unpredictable.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Sara"]}, "docId": "110307pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "CD", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "WP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "CC", "JJ", "CC", "JJS", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "CC", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 490, "question": "I think that's a smart move but how did you come to decide the way you were going to take it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "POS", "DT", "NN", "NN", "CC", "WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 491, "answer": "Well, it was Sara's creation but I will say what I think makes our show work is that you have five very different women who are all smart and funny and honest and they're not afraid to speak the truth and speak their mind.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110307pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "CD", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "CC", "RB", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 499, "question": "What's the one thing you think the viewers keep coming back to?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "CD", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "VBG", "RB", "TO", "."], "aSentId": 500, "answer": "I would say the number one issue is probably marital problems, or just relationship problems.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110307pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 503, "question": "More lashings of sex?", "question_pos_tagged": ["JJR", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 504, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110307pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 505, "question": "Because they're getting not enough of it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "RB", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 506, "answer": "Or too much.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110307pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 515, "question": "Sara, was that the concept you had originally?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 516, "answer": "Well, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110307pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 523, "question": "What do you all think of \"The View\"?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "DT", "VBP", "IN", "``", "DT", "NNP", "''", "."], "aSentId": 524, "answer": "We think it's great.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110307pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "VBN", "NN", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "WRB", "``", "DT", "NNP", "''", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 526, "question": "Do you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 527, "answer": "I was on bed rest 13 years ago when \"The View\" started.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110307pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 534, "question": "Rivals?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "aSentId": 535, "answer": "I love it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110307pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 563, "question": "What do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 564, "answer": "I think we have come a long way.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110307pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 567, "question": "Talking?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "."], "aSentId": 568, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110307pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 606, "question": "What does banning from in Britain?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 607, "answer": "You're not allowed on the show.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Britain"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110307pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 611, "question": "Me?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "."], "aSentId": 612, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110307pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJS", ",", "DT", "JJS", "."], "qSentId": 620, "question": "Do you think that was a prize?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 621, "answer": "The best, the best.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110307pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "PRP$", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "PRP$", ":", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 661, "question": "Where is the handbag?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 662, "answer": "I keep it in my -- I have it in my -- where I keep my things.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110307pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", ",", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 667, "question": "At what?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "."], "aSentId": 668, "answer": "At dancing, singing.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110307pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 675, "question": "Do you have a piece of tape on that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 676, "answer": "I wish we had.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110307pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "TO", "VB", ",", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 694, "question": "How can you say \"failed\" and \"prodigy\"?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "``", "VBN", "''", "CC", "``", "NN", "''", "."], "aSentId": 695, "answer": "That's what I was meant to be, failed.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110307pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", ":", "EX", "VBZ", "VBN", "NNS", "VBN", "CC", "NNS", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 702, "question": "Can you two continue this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "CD", "VBP", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 703, "answer": "We should mention because our boss is here from -- there's ten days left and people want to be judged by us.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110307pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "DT", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "CC", "IN", "VBZ", "RB", "WP", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 727, "question": "What life's like these days?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NN", "POS", "NN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 728, "answer": "It's a sad statement on humanity and we all love a train wreck, you know, and that's basically what it is.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110307pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", ",", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "``", "NNP", ",", "NN", ",", "''", "CC", "DT", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 737, "question": "Do you find any of what Charlie's doing funny in a dark way?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "IN", "WP", "NNP", "POS", "VBG", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 738, "answer": "In the beginning I thought funny, some of the statements, \"Winner, duh,\" and all that.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Charlie"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110307pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJR", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 746, "question": "You have been in the business 30 years now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CD", "NNS", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 747, "answer": "More than 30 years.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110307pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 761, "question": "The secret?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 762, "answer": "How do you avoid going off the rails.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110307pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "CD", "JJ", "NNS", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 773, "question": "How many shows do you do a year?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 774, "answer": "I still do 200 live shows a year.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America", "Britain", "Canada"]}, "docId": "110307pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 775, "question": "All around America?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 776, "answer": "America, Britain, Canada.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110307pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 784, "question": "You fly all around America?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 785, "answer": "Right.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110307pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 786, "question": "But you like to come back, don't you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "RB", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 787, "answer": "I need to be home.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110307pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 806, "question": "Who got you on twitter?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 807, "answer": "You did.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110307pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "CC", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "VBG", "NN", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 838, "question": "How do you have to lead your life, given the condition that you have?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 839, "answer": "First and foremost, I have a loving family, my wife is a saint.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110307pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 842, "question": "It's a fulltime thing for you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 843, "answer": "It's who I am.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["Thursday", "March 31st"]}, "docId": "110307pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "``", "JJ", "NNP", ",", "''", "NNP", ",", "NNP", "CD", ",", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 874, "question": "When does it air?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 875, "answer": "Right after \"American Idol,\" Thursday, March 31st, on FOX.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110307pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 876, "question": "You being annoying to people?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBG", "VBG", "TO", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 877, "answer": "Not me.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]